Finding Aid for the Colonial Court Records Group, 1665-1787 SR.401
State Archives of North Carolina
- Court Minutes and Dockets, 1680-1770; SR.401.1; 401.1; CCR 115 - CCR 138; CCR 146 - CCR 147; CCR 189; Dockets Minutes; 10.200; Colonial Courts; Court of Assize; General Court; Supreme Courts of Justice (Box Minutes and Dockets (unbound), 1680-1764, Item General Court Papers, Minutes, 1693-1695, It
  - Vice-Admiralty Papers, Vol. I, 1697-1738; CCR 142; Colonial Courts
  - Vice-Admiralty Papers, Vol. II, 1739-1746; CCR 143; Colonial Courts
  - Vice-Admiralty Papers, Vol. III, 1746-1753; CCR 144; Colonial Courts
  - Vice-Admiralty Papers, Vol. IV, 1754-1759, n.d.; CCR 145; Colonial Courts
  - Supreme Court Reference Docket, March (Edenton District), 1755; CCR 146; General Court (Folder Supreme Court Reference Docket, March (Edenton District))
  - Supreme Court Reference Docket October 1755, April 1756 (Edenton District), 1755-1756; CCR 146; General Court (Folder Supreme Court Reference Docket October 1755, April 1756 (Edenton District))
  - Court of Assize, Debts to be Proved at the Assizes, Bath, Wilmington, and New Bern, 1746; CCR 146; General Court (Folder Court of Assize, Debts to be Proved at the Assizes, Bath, Wilmington, and New Bern)
  - Reference Docquet General Court, March 1752, March 1753, September 1754, 1752-1754; CCR 146; General Court (Folder Reference Docquet General Court, March 1752, March 1753, September 1754)
  - General Court, List of Jurors (partial) (General Court and General Sessions, Edenton), 1739-1746; CCR 146; General Court (Folder General Court, List of Jurors (partial) (General Court and General Sessions, Edenton))
  - Court of Assize, Docquets for the Assizes [Bath, New Bern, Wilmington], 1741; CCR 146; General Court (Folder Court of Assize, Docquets for the Assizes [Bath, New Bern, Wilmington])
  - Court of Assizes, Oyer and Terminer Dockets and Minutes, 1739-1740; CCR 147; General Court (Folder Court of Assizes, Oyer and Terminer Dockets and Minutes)
  - Court of Assizes, Bath Town, New Bern, and Wilmington, 1742; CCR 147; General Court (Folder Court of Assizes, Bath Town, New Bern, and Wilmington)
  - Court of Assize, Oyer & Terminer and General Goal Delivery, Indictment, May, 1741; CCR 147; General Court (Folder Court of Assize, Oyer & Terminer and General Goal Delivery, Indictment, May)
  - Minutes, Precinct of Shaftsbury, April, 1680; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Precinct of Shaftsbury, April)
  - Minutes, March, 1682; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, March)
  - Minutes, Feb., June, Sept., 1683; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Feb., June, Sept.)
  - Minutes, Feb., Apr., June, Oct., Dec., 1684; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Feb., Apr., June, Oct., Dec.)
  - Minutes, Apr., Oct., Nov., 1685; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Apr., Oct., Nov.)
  - Minutes, July, Oct., Dec., 1686; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, July, Oct., Dec.)
  - Minutes, Oct., Nov., Dec., 1687; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Oct., Nov., Dec.)
  - Minutes, Feb., 1691; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Feb.)
  - Minutes, Mar., 1694; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Mar.)
  - Minutes, General Court, Nov., 1696; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court, Nov.)
  - Minutes, General Court, Chancery Court, Oct., 1697; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court, Chancery Court, Oct.)
  - Minutes, References and Docket, General and Chancery Court, March, 1698; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, References and Docket, General and Chancery Court, March)
  - Minutes, July, 1700; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, July)
  - Minutes, Mar., 1702; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Mar.)
  - Minutes, References, General Court, March; Special Court, Nov., 1705; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, References, General Court, March; Special Court, Nov.)
  - Minutes, General Court, Aug., Oct., 1706; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court, Aug., Oct.)
  - Minutes, Council, Nov., 1706; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Council, Nov.)
  - Minutes, General Court, Mar., July, Oct., 1707; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court, Mar., July, Oct.)
  - Minutes, General Court, Mar., July, 1708; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court, Mar., July)
  - Minutes, General Court, July, Oct., 1712; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court, July, Oct.)
  - Minutes, General Court, July, Oct., 1713; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court, July, Oct.)
  - Minutes, General Court, Mar., Oct., 1714; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court, Mar., Oct.)
  - Minutes, General Court, Mar., July; Special Court, Apr., 1715; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court, Mar., July; Special Court, Apr.)
  - Minutes, General Court, Mar., July, Aug., Oct., 1716; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court, Mar., July, Aug., Oct.)
  - Minutes, General Court, Mar., 1717; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court, Mar.)
  - Minutes, Court of Oyer and Terminer and General Gaol Delivery, Oct., 1718; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Court of Oyer and Terminer and General Gaol Delivery, Oct.)
  - Minutes, Court of Oyer and Terminer, Mar.; General Court, July, Oct., 1719; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Court of Oyer and Terminer, Mar.; General Court, July, Oct.)
  - Minutes of Commissioners to Examine Public Treasury, Nov. 1719-Sept. 1722, CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes of Commissioners to Examine Public Treasury, Nov. 1719-Sept. 1722)
  - Minutes, General Court, Oyer & Terminer, Mar., Apr., July, Oct., Nov., 1720; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court, Oyer & Terminer, Mar., Apr., July, Oct., Nov.)
  - Minutes, General Court, Oyer & Terminer, Mar., July, Aug., Oct., 1721; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court, Oyer & Terminer, Mar., July, Aug., Oct.)
  - Minutes, General Court, Oyer & Terminer, July, Oct.; Special Court Oyer & Ter., Aug., 1722; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court, Oyer & Terminer, July, Oct.; Special Court Oyer & Ter., Aug.)
  - Minutes, General Court, Oyer & Terminer, Mar., Oct., 1723; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court, Oyer & Terminer, Mar., Oct.)
  - Minutes, Geneal Court, Oyer & Terminer, Mar., Oct., 1724; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Geneal Court, Oyer & Terminer, Mar., Oct.)
  - Minutes, General Court, [Mar.], [1725]; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court, [Mar.])
  - Minutes, General Court of Oyer & Terminer and Goal Delivery, July, Oct., 1725; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court of Oyer & Terminer and Goal Delivery, July, Oct.)
  - Minutes, General Court of Oyer & Terminer and Goal Delivery, Mar., July, 1726; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court of Oyer & Terminer and Goal Delivery, Mar., July)
  - Minutes, General Court of Oyer & Terminer and Goal Delivery, March, 1727; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court of Oyer & Terminer and Goal Delivery, March)
  - Minutes, General Court, Oyer & Terminer, General Sessions, Mar., Apr., July, Aug., Oct., 1729; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court, Oyer & Terminer, General Sessions, Mar., Apr., July, Aug., Oct.)
  - Minutes, General Court of Sessions, April, 1730; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court of Sessions, April)
  - Minutes, Court of Oyer & Terminer, Dec., 1732; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Court of Oyer & Terminer, Dec.)
  - Minutes, Pasquotank Precinct, Jan., 1733; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Pasquotank Precinct, Jan.)
  - Minutes, Court of Oyer & Terminer, Assize, and Gen. Goal Delivery, June, 1733; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Court of Oyer & Terminer, Assize, and Gen. Goal Delivery, June)
  - Minutes, Court of Oyer & Terminer and Goal Delivery, Dec., 1734; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Court of Oyer & Terminer and Goal Delivery, Dec.)
  - Minutes, Court of Oyer & Terminer and Goal Delivery, Jan., Nov., 1738; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Court of Oyer & Terminer and Goal Delivery, Jan., Nov.)
  - Minutes, Court of Assize, Apr., May, Aug., Sept., 1740; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Court of Assize, Apr., May, Aug., Sept.)
  - Minutes, Court of Assize, Apr., May, Sept.; Docket, Apr., 1741; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Court of Assize, Apr., May, Sept.; Docket, Apr.)
  - Minutes and Docket, Court of Assize, Apr., 1742; CCR 214; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes and Docket, Court of Assize, Apr.)
  - Minutes, Court of Oyer and Terminer, Dec., 1743; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Court of Oyer and Terminer, Dec.)
  - Minutes, Court of Assize, Oct., 1753; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Court of Assize, Oct.)
  - Minutes, Court of Assize, April, 1754; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Court of Assize, April)
  - Minutes, Unidentified, n.d.; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Unidentified)
  - Minutes, Court of Vice Admiralty, 1706-1764; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, Court of Vice Admiralty)
  - Minutes, General Court and Misc (during reign of Queen Ann), CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Minutes, General Court and Misc (during reign of Queen Ann))
  - Docket to Gen. Court, 1697; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Docket to Gen. Court)
  - Dockets, 1705-1706; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Dockets)
  - Dockets, References and Attachments, 1712-1719; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Dockets, References and Attachments)
  - Dockets, References and Attachments, 1720-1729; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Dockets, References and Attachments)
  - Dockets, References Continuances Docket, 1724; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Dockets, References Continuances Docket)
  - Dockets, Docket Fragments, 1727-1735; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Dockets, Docket Fragments)
  - Dockets, Reference Dockets, 1732; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Dockets, Reference Dockets)
  - Dockets, Assizes and Wilmington, 1743; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Dockets, Assizes and Wilmington)
  - Dockets and References, 1741-1749; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Dockets and References)
  - Dockets and References, 1750-1757; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Dockets and References)
  - Dockets, Crown Docket, Supreme Courts, 1757-1764; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Dockets, Crown Docket, Supreme Courts)
  - Dockets, n.d.; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Dockets)
  - Writts, 1732-1733; CCR 215; Colonial Courts (Folder Writts)
- Civil and Criminal Action Papers, 1680-1759; SR.401.2; 401.2; CCR 148 - CCR 178; CCR 193 - CCR 196; 1.200; General Court; Court of Assize; Supreme Court of Justice (Box Civil and Criminal Action Papers, Box Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  This series is arranged chronologically by year and may contain documents from the same case from previous and following years. Folders with no date (n.d.) are arranged according to year by best estimation and/or by the signature of the active clerk or justice.
  This series contains documents pertaining to civil and criminal court cases taking place in the Albemarle County General Court and precinct courts including Rowan, Pasquotank, Currituck, Perquimans, and Chowan Precincts as well as the later Bath County Court and a few pieces from the Norfolk County Court in Virginia. Materials include case narratives, depositions, summons and attachments, arrest warrants, bonds, petitions, custody claims, debt bills and acquittals. Case subject include debt, plea of trespass, plea of the case, merchandise and goods appropriation, defamation, land sales, theft and burglary, witch accusations, murder, property (including slaves), insubordination within the militia, unlawful cohabitation and a case regarding roads.
  - Depositions of Robert Holden (Majesties Customs Collector), 1680; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Depositions of Robert Holden (Majesties Customs Collector))
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1681; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1684; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1685; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1688; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1689; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1690; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1691; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1692; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1693; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1694; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1695; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1696; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1697; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1698; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1699; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1700; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1701; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1702; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1703; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1704; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1705; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1706; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1707; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1708; CCR 148; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1709; CCR 149; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1710; CCR 149; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1711; CCR 149; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1712; CCR 149; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1713; CCR 149; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1714; CCR 149; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1715; CCR 149; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1716; CCR 149; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1717; CCR 149; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1718; CCR 150; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Actions Papers, 1719; CCR 150; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Actions Papers)
  - Civil and Criminal Action Papers-no date, [1680-1719]; CCR 150; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Action Papers-no date)
  - Civil and Criminal Action Papers-no date, [1680-1717]; CCR 150; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Action Papers-no date)
  - n.d. (Signed by Wm. Glover, Clk. Of Court), [1695-1698]; CCR 150; General Court (Folder n.d. (signed by Wm. Glover, Clk. Of Court))
  - n.d. (signed by N. Chevin, Clk. Of Court), [1697-1703]; CCR 150; General Court (Folder n.d. (signed by N. Chevin, Clk. Of Court))
  - n.d. (signed by Thos Snoden, Clk. Of Court), [1703-1705]; CCR 150; General Court (Folder n.d. (signed by Thos Snoden, Clk. Of Court))
  - n.d. (signed by Ch. Justice Chr. Gale), [1703-1708, 1712]; CCR 150; General Court (Folder n.d. (signed by Ch. Justice Chr. Gale))
  - n.d. (signed by Robert Buckner. Clk. Of Court), [1711-1712]; CCR 150; General Court (Folder n.d. (signed by Robert Buckner. Clk. Of Court))
  - n.d. (signed by Tobias Knight, Secretary), [1712]; CCR 150; General Court (Folder n.d. (signed by Tobias Knight, Secretary))
  - Civil and Criminal Action Papers-no date, [1718-1719]; CCR 150; General Court (Folder Civil and Criminal Action Papers-no date)
  - Petitions, n.d., [1681-1759]; CCR 150; General Court (Folder Petitions)
  - Pleas, Depositions, etc., n.d., [1681-1759]; CCR 150; General Court (Folder Pleas, Depositions, etc.)
- Civil and Criminal Action Papers, General Court, 1720-1754; SR.401.3; 401.3; CCR 179 - CCR 186.3; CCR 197; Inventories; 14.800; General Court
  This series contains documents relating to civil and criminal suits tried in the North Carolina court system. Cases take place at the general court, precinct courts, Bath County Court, Edenton courthouse, and in other various counties. Materials for both subseries include narratives of the cases by the plaintiffs and defendants, pleas, depositions, arrest warrants and attachments, summons, debt bills, bonds, recognizances, and petitions.
  - Civil Action Papers, 1720-1754, nd; SR.401.3.1; 12.800; General Court (Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1720-1722, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1722-1723, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1723, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1724, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1725, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1725-1726, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1726-1727, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1727-1728, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1728-1729, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1729-1730, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1731, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1732, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1733-1734, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1734-1735, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1735-1736, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1736, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1736-1737, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1737, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1737-1738, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1738-1739, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1739, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1740, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1741, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1741-1742, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1742-1743, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1743-1744, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1744, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1745, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, 1746-1754, Box General Court, Civil Action Papers, n.d. [1720-1746])
    This subseries is arranged chronologically by year and may contain documents belonging to the same case from previous and following years.
    This subseries contains civil cases tried in the North Carolina colonial courts. Case subjects for the Civil Action Papers subseries include debt, merchandise and goods misappropriation, goods owed, plea of trespass, plea of the case, land disputes, and custody.
    - General Court-Civil, 1720; CCR 151; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil)
    - General Court, Civil, 1721; CCR 151; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 1, 1722; CCR 151; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 1)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 1.1, 1722; CCR 151; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 1.1)
    - General Court-Civil, folder 1.2, 1722; CCR 151; General Court (Folder General Court-Civil, folder 1.2)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 2, 1722; CCR 152; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 2)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 2.1, 1722; CCR 152; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 2.1)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 3, 1722; CCR 152; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 3)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 3.1, 1722; CCR 152; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 3.1)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 1, 1723; CCR 152; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 1)
    - General Court, Civil, 1723; CCR 153; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil,)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 1, 1723; CCR 153; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 1)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 1.1, 1723; CCR 153; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 1.1)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 1.2, 1723; CCR 153; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 1.2)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 2, 1723; CCR 153; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 2)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 2.1, 1723; CCR 153; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 2.1)
    - General Court, Civil, 1724; CCR 154; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 1, 1724; CCR 154; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 1)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 1.1, 1724; CCR 154; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 1.1)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 2, 1724; CCR 154; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 2)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 3, 1724; CCR 154; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 3)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 3.1, 1724; CCR 154; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 3.1)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 4, 1724; CCR 154; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 4)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 1, 1725; CCR 155; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 1)
    - Genreal Court, Civil, folder 1.1, 1725; CCR 155; General Court (Folder Genreal Court, Civil, folder 1.1)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 1.2, 1725; CCR 155; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 1.2)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 2, 1725; CCR 155; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 2)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 2.1, 1725; CCR 155; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 2.1)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 2.2, 1725; CCR 155; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 2.2)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 3, 1725; CCR 155; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 3)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 3.1, 1725; CCR 155; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 3.1)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 4, 1725; CCR 156; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 4)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 4.1, 1725; CCR 156; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 4.1)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 4.2, 1725; CCR 156; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 4.2)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 1, 1726; CCR 156; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 1)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 1.1, 1726; CCR 156; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 1.1)
    - General Court, Civil, folder 2, 1726; CCR 156; General Court (Folder General Court, Civil, folder 2)